





RÉSUMÉ

— Hello! I'm skilled frontend developer with 7 years of experience in UI/UX design, application development, and database modelling. I strive to craft precise, responsive, fast, easy-to-use environments with both strong purpose and great looks.

EXPERIENCE

1st October 2016 – present

Senior full-stack developer at **Dutchstar**

• build, test, and deploy applications written with React + Redux and Phalcon + MySQL

25th May 2014 - forever

Married to **(a)** Lyudmyla Mandzyuk

• do all the different things

1st September 2012 – 30th September 2016

Service Center Databases Lead at <u>Sumitomo Electric Bordnetze</u> Ukraine

- managed MySQL multi-master clusters, Oracle failover clusters, Microsoft SQL mirrored/replicated servers (monitoring, backup/restore, users/groups/roles, schemas)
- built and benchmarked fast, efficient SQL queries
- optimized database engines, indexes, etc.
- crafted web dashboards, reports using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SQL

1st February 2011 – 30th September 2016

IT production subdivision manager at <u>Sumitomo Electric</u> <u>Bordnetze</u> Ukraine

- designed computer-aided manufacturing processes
- interconnected different production systems' databases (push or pull data using replication, triggers, scheduled events, cron jobs)
- built high-availability systems, minimized downtime
- designed and built BDE (BetriebsDatenErfassung) data aggregator system designed to assist in planning, manufacturing, monitoring and controlling
- analyzed and transformed data
- wrote docs, manuals, guidelines, and memos

14th February 2008 – 31st January 2011

Software engineer at Sumitomo Electric Bordnetze Ukraine

- designed UI and UX for native applications and web pages
- built simple apps to assist in manufacturing process using Delphi, VB, Java, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, SQL
- managed Microsoft SQL, MySQL, and Firebird databases

February 2006 – August 2007

Graphic designer at Terminal

 designed booklets, flyers, business cards, posters using Adobe CS (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)

LANGUAGES

UKRAINIAN RUSSIAN ENGLISH

SKILLS

HTML CSS JS PHP BOILERPLATE
BOOTSTRAP SEMANTIC UI LESS SASS
JQUERY ANGULARJS REACT LODASH
GRUNT GULP BOWER WEBPACK
NODEJS NPM MICROSOFT OFFICE
PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR DELPHI
VB VBA VBSCRIPT LINUX WINDOWS
MACOS MYSQL POSTGRESQL
MICROSOFT SQL DB2 CCNA ITIL

CHARACTER

EXPLORER STRAIGHTFORWARD
DEVOTED PEDANTIC AGNOSTIC
CONTENTIOUS PROCRASTINATOR
RELEVANT EMPATHETIC STORYTELLER
CONFIDENT CONSISTENT
CHALLENGING

LIKES 😃

HUMOUR PATIENCE DOGS MOVIES
AAPL FC BARCELONA JÄGERMEISTER
L'VIV FRISBEE • MIDNIGHT BLUE
ELECTROPOP CUCINA ITALIANA '80S
SELF-EDUCATION DEMOCRACY
ATTENTION TO DETAILS GRAMMAR
SPELLCHECK SEMANTICS MINI-SERIES
RYAN GOSLING EMMA STONE

DISLIKES 😩

OWN BAD HABITS POLITICS RACISM ASS-KISSERS VODKA INCOMPETENCE ENVY GOLF • CHARTREUSE INSECTS METRO PREJUDICE REALITY-SHOWS JŪRMALA

EDUCATION

December 2005 - April 2006

- managed inkjet plotters and printers
- built websites using Macromedia Dreamweaver, Macromedia Flash (ActionScript)

April 2004 – December 2004

System administrator at Pyramid

- managed a network of dozen Windows workstations and one Linux gateway (DHCP, DNS, proxy, ACLs)
- kept PCs health (install OS over PXE, backup/restore, antivirus, software updates, hardware upgrades etc.)
- ••• couldn't do much really for the first few years...

6th October 1986

Born in Ternopil, Ukraine — Thanks, mom and dad!

Certificates of CCNA Course Completion at Cisco Networking Academy Program

1st September 2003 – 30th June 2008 Bachelor's degree in computer science at Ternopil National Technical University

1st September 1993 – 21st June 2003
Certificate of graduation at №20
Middle School of General
Education

1st October 1995 – 23rd May 1999 Certificate of graduation at Ternopil Art School for Children